{
    "subject": "resource/Il_Politecnico",
    "predicate": "ontology/founder",
    "object": "resource/Giulio_Einaudi",
    "human_readable": "Il Politecnico was founded by Giulio Einaudi.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9885332584381104,
            "question": "Is Giulio Einaudi the founder of Il Politecnico?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9193642139434814,
            "question": "Who founded Il Politecnico?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9068568348884583,
            "question": "By whom was Il Politecnico established?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8815680742263794,
            "question": "Who established Il Politecnico?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.85165935754776,
            "question": "What is the name of the founder of Il Politecnico?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7691841125488281,
            "question": "Which university was founded in relation to Giulio Einaudi?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7671019434928894,
            "question": "What did Giulio Einaudi establish?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7622965574264526,
            "question": "What is the name of the university founded by Giulio Einaudi?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7001274228096008,
            "question": "What institution did Giulio Einaudi found?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6341266632080078,
            "question": "With what institution is Giulio Einaudi associated?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Il Politecnico was founded by Giulio Einaudi.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5315_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What institution did Giulio Einaudi found?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5315_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the university founded by Giulio Einaudi?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5315_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What did Giulio Einaudi establish?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5315_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5315_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5315_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5315_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5315_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5315_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5315_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5315_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5315_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5315_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5315_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents mention that Giulio Einaudi was the publisher of Il Politecnico, but there is no information supporting that he was involved in founding the magazine. The founders and establishment details for Il Politecnico are not provided in the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "Il Politecnico mentioned in the context refers to two different entities - one being a cultural and literary magazine published between 1945 and 1947, and the other being the Politecnico di Milano, which is a university founded in 1863. Giulio Einaudi was indeed the publisher of the former Il Politecnico magazine, but he did not found it nor has any connection with the latter Politecnico di Milano.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}